Guide to the Roland Park Company Records, ca. 1891-1962
Roland Park Company Records, ca. 1891-1962
- Series I. Correspondence
  - E-G, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - H, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - I-L, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - M, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - M, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - N-S, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - S, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - T-Y, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - P, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - R-S, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - T-V, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - W-Z, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - A-B Bouton personal and country club, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - C-F Bouton personal and country club, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - G-M Bouton personal and country club, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - N-Y Bouton personal and country club, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - A-D Bouton personal, 1891-1892 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - E-G Bouton personal, 1891-1892 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - H Bouton personal, 1891-1892 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - I-M Bouton personal, 1891-1892 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - N-W Bouton personal, 1891-1892 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Telegrams, 1891-1892 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - A-B, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - B, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - B, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - C, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - G-S, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - S, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - S-W, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - B, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - C, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - C, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - H-W, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - W, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - A-B, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - C-D, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - E-M, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - M-S, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - U-W, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - A-D, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - D, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - D-J, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - K-N, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - O-S (Olmsted), 1906 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - T-Y, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - B-J, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - M-S, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - A-D, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - M, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - P-S, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - W-Y, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - A-C, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - C, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - C, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - D-S, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - T, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - T, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - W-Y, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - A-D, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - G-M, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - P-R, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - H-L, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - M, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - M, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - N-T, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - B-D, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - G, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - K-M, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - M-R, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - S-T, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - T-W, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - A-D, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - G-J, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - K-N, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - N, 1905 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - N, 1905 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - N, 1905 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - P-S, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - S-V, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - A-E, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - H-L, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - M-N, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - P-W, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - A-C, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - E-F, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - G-O, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - P-R, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - S-W, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - A-G, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - H-M, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - P-R, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - S, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - V-W, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - A-F, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - H-L, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - M-P, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - R-S, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - S-V, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - W, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - A, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - B, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - C-E, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - F-G, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - H-K, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - K-L, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - C, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - D-E, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - G-L, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - M, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Q-S, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - T-Z, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - A-C, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - D-H, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - K-M, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - N-S, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - T-Z, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - B-D, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - F-J, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - L, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - M-R, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - S-W, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - B-C, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - D-H, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - K-M, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - M-O, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - R-T, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - A, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - A-B, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - B, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - B-C, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - C, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - C, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - D-E, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - D, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - E-F, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - F, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - G, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - H, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - H-J, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - A-H Bouton personal, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - L-R Bouton personal, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - S-Y Bouton personal, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - J-K, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - L, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Mc, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - M, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - M, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - N, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - O-P, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - P-Q, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - R, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - S, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - S, 1906 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - T, 1906 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - U-V, 1906 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - W, 1906 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - W-Z, 1906 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - A, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - B, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - B, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - B, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - C, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - C, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - D-E, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - F, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - G, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - G, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - G, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - H, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - H, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - I-J, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - K, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - L, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - M, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - M, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - N-O, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - P, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - P-Q, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - R, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - S, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - S, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - T-V, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - W, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - W-Z, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - B-C, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - C, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - C-U, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - A-B, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - C-D, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - E-F, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - G-W, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - A-D, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - G-N, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - N-Y Olmsted, Price and McLanahan Architects (Philadelphia), Wyatt and Nolting, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - B, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - C-G, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - H, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - I-M, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - B-C, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - C-M, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - P-T, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - W-Y, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - A-J, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - K-M, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - M-R, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - S-Y, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - A-H, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - K-M, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - N-S, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - A-C, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - G, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - M, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - M-W, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - B-K, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - N (Herman Noss and Sons), 1907 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - N (Herman Noss and Sons), 1907 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - A-D, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - G-M, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - N-V, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - A-O (advertisement for architect), 1907 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - E-O, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - P-W, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - A-C, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - E-P, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - R-W, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - A-I, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - K-P, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - S-W, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - A-K, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - L-R, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - S-W, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - A-D, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - E-G, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - H-W, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - C-G, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - H-Q, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - R-Z, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - D-S, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - T-Z, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - B-J, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - K-M, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - M-S, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - T-Y, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - B-I, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - M-S, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - W-Y, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - A-E, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - G-M, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - N-R, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - S-W, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - B-H, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - N-W, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - A-G Bouton personal, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - J-L Bouton personal, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - M-R Bouton personal, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - S-U Bouton personal, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - A, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - B, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - C, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - C, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - D, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - E, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - F-G, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - G-H, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - H, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - H-J, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - K, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - L, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - M, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - M, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - N-O, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - P, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - P-Q, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - R, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - S, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - S, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - S, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - T-V, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - W, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - W-Z, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - A-G (Bouton personal), 1908 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - H-M (Bouton personal), 1908 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - N-S (Bouton personal), 1908 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - T-W (Bouton personal), 1908 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - B (land ownership, Bernard and Son Attorneys), 1908 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - B, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - B, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - C Cole (County Clerk), 1908 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - F-W, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - A-B, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - C, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - C, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - E-K, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - M-W, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - B, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - B, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - C-G, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - I-S, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - T-W, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - A-C, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - D-M, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - M-P, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - R-S, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - T-W, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - A-D, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - D-E, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - H-M, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - N-U, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - V-Y, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - A-K, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - M, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - A-K, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - M, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - M, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - M-O, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - P-W, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - B-D, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - G-N, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - N-S, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - S-V, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - A-G, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - H-N, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - N-W, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - A-C, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - C-E, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - F-R, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - S-W, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - A-D, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - F-N, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - P-W, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - A-C, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - D-G, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - H-N, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - P-W, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - A-H, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - K-M (Mainly work orders), 1908 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - M-Q, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - R-S, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - T-Z, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - A-D, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - E-K, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - L-M, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - N-S, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - T-W, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - B-D, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - E-G, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - H-L (Sewerage Commission), 1908 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - M-P, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - R-S, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - S-W, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - A-B Topographical survey, University Parkway, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - B-G letter complains re neighbor's house (Boullemet), 1908 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - H-S Professor J. F. Hopkins, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - T-W, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - B, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - G, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - J-N, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - P-W, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - A-B, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - C, 1909 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - L-W, 1909 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - C Carey, Piper and Hall legal correspondence, 1909 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - G-W, 1909 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - A-B, 1909 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - C-D, 1909 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - E-W, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - A-D, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - H-O, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - R-W, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - B, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - E-G, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - H-W, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - A-K, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - L-P, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - R-Y, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - A-L, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - M, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - M-R, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - S-W, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - A-K, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - M, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - S-W, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - B-M, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - N, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - R-W, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - B-G, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - H-M, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - N-W, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - A-C, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - E-G, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - H-W, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - A-C, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - F-G, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - H-M, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - N-P, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - S-W, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - C-G, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - G-H, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - K-R, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - S-W, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - A-C, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - D-F City Engineer and Dept. PW, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - G-L, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - M-W, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - A-D, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - F-M, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - N-S, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - T-Z, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - A-G, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - H-K, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - L-P, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - R, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - S-Y, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - A-B, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - B-E, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - G-J, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - B-S, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - T-W, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - B-L, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - M, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - M-S, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - T-W, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - A-D, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - G-M, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - N-P, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - S, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - A-H, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - H-M, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - N-P, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - H-M, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - N-P, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - S-T, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - A-H, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - H-W, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - A (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - B (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - B (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - B (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - C (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - C (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - D (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - E (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - F (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - G (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - G (miscellaneous), 1909 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - H (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - H (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - I-J (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - K (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - K-L (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - L (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - M (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - M (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - N (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - O-P (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - P-R (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - R (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - R (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - S (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - S (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - S (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - T (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - T-W (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - W (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - W-Z (miscellaneous files), 1909 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - A-D [Bouton personal], 1909 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - E-M [Bouton personal], 1909 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - L-R [Bouton personal], 1909 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - S-W [Bouton personal], 1909 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - A-B, 1910 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - B, 1910 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - C-W, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - C, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - D-W, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - A, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - B, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - F-R, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - U-W, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - A-N, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - O (Olmsted), 1910 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - R-W, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - A-B, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - B-E, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - G-W, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - B-G, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - M-T, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - T-W, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - A-B, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - C-R, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - A-B, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - C-R, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - S (Sage Fndn. Homes Corp.), 1910 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - W-Y, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - B-K, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - L-P, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - R-Y, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - A-K, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - M, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - M-W, 1910 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - A-H, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - M, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - M, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - N-W, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - B, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - D-N, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - R-T, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - A-H, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - K-T, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - W, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - A-B, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - C, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - C-L, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - M-W, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - A-C, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - D-G, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - M-N, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - P (Palmer Jr.), 1910 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - R-V, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - A-F, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - G-I, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - K-R, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - S-W, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - A-E, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - F, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - G-W, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - A-E, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - G-L, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - M-P, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - R-Z, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - A-L, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - M-R, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - S-Z, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - B-H, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - L-N, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - P-Y, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - B, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - C-L, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - M-N, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - P-W, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - A-H, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - H-L, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - M-T, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - A-C, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - G-P, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - R [Roads Maint. Corp.] (RP R and M Corp.) Winslow Ave. houses Jan. 1910 plans Lots 1-8 Block 3 Plat 1 RP (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - R-W [Road Maint. Corp.] (RP R and M Corp.), 1910 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - A (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - B (miscellanous), 1910 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - B (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - C (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - C (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - D (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - K-R, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - E (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - E-F (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - G (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - H (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - H (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - I-K (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - L (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - L-M (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - M (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - M (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - N-O (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - P-Q (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - R (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - S (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - S (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - T-V (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - W (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - W-Z (miscellaneous), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - A-F (Bouton personal), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - G-M (Bouton personal), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - O-Y (Bouton personal), 1910 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Letters (1-151), 1911 (Box 57)
  - Letters (151-443), 1911 (Box 58)
  - Letters (444-840), 1911 (Box 59)
  - Letters (841-954), 1911 (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous (A-L), 1911 (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous (Mc-St), 1911 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous (Su-Z) Bouton personal, 1911 (Box 63)
  - Letters (1-125), 1912 (Box 64)
  - Letters (126-294), 1912 (Box 65)
  - Letters (295-453), 1912 (Box 66)
  - Letters (457-723), 1912 (Box 67)
  - Letters (724-882), 1912 (Box 68)
  - Letters (883-954) Misc., A-B, 1912 (Box 69)
  - Miscellaneous (C-G), 1912 (Box 70)
  - Miscellaneous (H-O), 1912 (Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous (P-Wa), 1912 (Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous (Wb-Z), 1912 (Box 73)
  - Guilford Estimates, 1912 (Box 73)
  - Allen and Shreve, 1912 (Box 73)
  - W.H.H. Allan Construction Co., 1912 (Box 73)
  - Willis Fox Co., 1912 (Box 73)
  - Sage Foundation, 1911-1912 (Box 73)
  - Bouton personal, 1912 (Box 73)
  - Letters (1-97), 1913 (Box 74)
  - Letters (98-278), 1913 (Box 75)
  - Letters (279-485), 1913 (Box 76)
  - Letters (486- 873), 1913 (Box 77)
  - Letters (874-972), 1913 (Box 78)
  - Letters (Miscellaneous A-Cz), 1913 (Box 79)
  - Letters (Miscellaneous D-K), 1913 (Box 80)
  - Miscellaneous (L-P), 1913 (Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous (Q-Z), 1913 (Box 82)
  - Bouton personal, 1913 (Box 83)
  - Mr. Harwood, 1913 (Box 83)
  - Purchasing Department-Henry and Williams, 1913 (Box 83)
  - Letters (1-124), 1914 (Box 84)
  - Letters (125-373), 1914 (Box 85)
  - Letters (374-608), 1914 (Box 86)
  - Letters (609-972), 1914 (Box 87)
  - Miscellaneous (A-G), 1914 (Box 88)
  - Miscellaneous (H-O), 1914 (Box 89)
  - Miscellaneous (P-Z), 1914 (Box 90)
  - Bouton personal, 1914 (Box 91)
  - Elmwood Laud Co., 1914 (Box 91)
  - Harwood Personal, 1914 (Box 91)
  - Letters (1-208), 1915 (Box 92)
  - Letters (209-575), 1915 (Box 93)
  - Letters(576-972), 1915 (Box 94)
  - Letters (Miscellaneous A-F), 1915 (Box 95)
  - Miscellaneous (G-O), 1915 (Box 96)
  - Miscellaneous (P-Z), 1915 (Box 97)
  - Bouton personal, 1915 (Box 98)
  - Harwood personal, 1915 (Box 98)
  - G.J. Smith Estate, 1915 (Box 98)
  - Letters(1-185), 1916 (Box 99)
  - Letters(186-607), 1916 (Box 100)
  - Letters(608-972), 1916 (Box 101)
  - Miscellaneous (A-G), 1916 (Box 102)
  - Miscellaneous (H-P), 1916 (Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous (Q-Z), 1916 (Box 104)
  - Bouton personal, 1916 (Box 105)
  - Harwood personal, 1916 (Box 105)
  - Suburbau Lumber Co., 1916 (Box 105)
  - G.J. Smith Estate, 1916 (Box 105)
  - Letters (1-216), 1917 (Box 106)
  - Letters (217-599), 1917 (Box 107)
  - Letters (600-972), 1917 (Box 108)
  - Miscellaneous (A-F), 1917 (Box 109)
  - Miscellaneous (G-M), 1917 (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous (N-T), 1917 (Box 111)